What's a side effect of loss that no one seems to notice?
That no matter how happy you may look,
it's still an opportunity for you to feel sad in an instant, you know?
And it's almost like if you were a balloon.
Imagine being a balloon and you stuck a pin in it.
Not just popped it, but just let the air seep out.
Yeah.
Like you just decompressing.
And then just go back to having fun again.
Right.
Like that may seem weird.
It's a pressure valve.
Yeah, it's like, but imagine somebody like you seeing it in somebody.
Like it's like, like people do that to you all the time.
I mean, as a cancer, that's my life.
Oh, I'm here chilling, chilling.
And I'm like, and we're back.
And it's not a sad cry.
It's like a, I don't even know.
Like just lamenting.
Just like, I just releasing.
Do you read a lot?
I do.
Okay.
Cause your vocab be hitting lamenting.
I'm like, I'm listening to you.
I'm like the words, you know, I love a word.